[
  {
    "counter":1,
    "center":[
      53.22141,
      -4.20329
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Llanfairpwllgwyngyll",
    "wrong":[
      "Mittelschaeffolsheim",
      "Nová Ves u Nového Města na Moravě",
      "Gschlachtenbretzingen"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":2,
    "center":[
      55.29002,
      25.65506
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Zvaigzdziakalnis",
    "wrong":[
      "Llanfairpwllgwyngyll",
      "Mittelschaeffolsheim",
      "Rhosllannerchrugog"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":3,
    "center":[
      53.077803,
      6.800737
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Annerveenschekanaal",
    "wrong":[
      "Rhosllannerchrugog",
      "Mittelschaeffolsheim",
      "Saint-Remy-en-Bouzemont-Saint-Genest-et-Isson"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":4,
    "center":[
      52.89228,
      17.69194
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Brzyskorzystewko",
    "wrong":[
      "Jazgarzewszczyzna",
      "Zvaigzdziakalnis",
      "Gschlachtenbretzingen"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":5,
    "center":[
      46.76081,
      17.15528
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Nemesboldogasszonyfa",
    "wrong":[
      "Przedmieście Szczebrzeszyńskie",
      "Jazgarzewszczyzna",
      "Zvaigzdziakalnis"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":6,
    "center":[
      49.539772,
      16.086488
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Nová Ves u Nového Města na Moravě",
    "wrong":[
      "Jazgarzewszczyzna",
      "Nemesboldogasszonyfa",
      "Przedmieście Szczebrzeszyńskie"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":7,
    "center":[
      48.700749,
      7.650879
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Mittelschaeffolsheim",
    "wrong":[
      "Nemesboldogasszonyfa",
      "Brzyskorzystewko",
      "Przedmieście Szczebrzeszyńskie"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":8,
    "center":[
      53.009966,
      -3.056333
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Rhosllannerchrugog",
    "wrong":[
      "Nemesboldogasszonyfa",
      "Zvaigzdziakalnis",
      "Gschlachtenbretzingen"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":9,
    "center":[
      52.06413,
      20.98436
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Jazgarzewszczyzna",
    "wrong":[
      "Gschlachtenbretzingen",
      "Przedmieście Szczebrzeszyńskie",
      "Annerveenschekanaal"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":10,
    "center":[
      47.506985,
      19.79249
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Jászfelsőszentgyörgy",
    "wrong":[
      "Nová Ves u Nového Města na Moravě",
      "Nemesboldogasszonyfa",
      "Gschlachtenbretzingen"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":11,
    "center":[
      49.08817,
      9.75404
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Gschlachtenbretzingen",
    "wrong":[
      "Zvaigzdziakalnis",
      "Annerveenschekanaal",
      "Nová Ves u Nového Města na Moravě"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":12,
    "center":[
      48.627415,
      4.649772
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Saint-Remy-en-Bouzemont-Saint-Genest-et-Isson",
    "wrong":[
      "Annerveenschekanaal",
      "Brzyskorzystewko",
      "Zvaigzdziakalnis"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":13,
    "center":[
      49.08817,
      9.75404
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Gschlachtenbretzingen",
    "wrong":[
      "Jazgarzewszczyzna",
      "Annerveenschekanaal"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":14,
    "center":[
      50.81814,
      22.76238
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Przedmieście Szczebrzeszyńskie",
    "wrong":[
      "Jazgarzewszczyzna",
      "Nemesboldogasszonyfa",
      "Mittelschaeffolsheim"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  }
]